我叫Oliver Queen
My name is Oliver Queen.
经历岛上地狱般的五年后
After five years on a hellish island,
我回来了 心怀一个目标...
I have come home with only one goal...
拯救这座城市
To save my city.
但为此我不能再像以前一样杀戮
But to do so, I can't be the killer I once was.
为了祭奠我的好友
To honor my friend's memory,
我必须重塑自己
I must be someone else.
我必须伪装自身
I must be something else.
"绿箭侠" 前情提要...
Previously on "Arrow"...
他已经没有利用价值了
This one's no longer of use to us.
等等 他还有利用价值
Wait. He could still be useful.
没错 一旦除掉他的那几个朋友
She's right. Once we get rid of his friends,
我们需要他带领我们去墓地
we'll need him to lead us to the grave.
你要回炼狱岛
You're going back to the island.
你已经失去了父亲
Look, you already lost your dad.
但是你母亲还在 她一定很想见你
Your mom, she's still here. And I'm sure she'd love to see you.
我不会去监狱看她
I'm not going to that prison.
这是唯一能够报复她的方式
It's the only way I know how to hurt her.
我真的很想恨你
And I want to hate you.
但是我做不到
But I can't.
我们之间没什么秘密可言
I didn't think that there were secrets kept between us.
妈妈... 你到底在隐瞒什么?
Mom... what are you hiding now?
我叫Moira Dearden Queen
My name is Moira Dearden Queen.
我是Queen氏实业的执行总裁
I am the acting CEO of Queen Consolidated.
愿上帝原谅 我辜负了这座城市
And, God forgive me, I have failed this city.
我被迫参与
I have been complicit in an undertaking
一项极其恐怖的阴谋...
with one horrible purpose...
摧毁贫民区的一切
to destroy the Glades and everyone in it.
如果你住在贫民区
If you reside in the glades,
请马上离开那里
please, you need to get out now.
你们和你们的孩子正命悬一线
Your lives and the lives of your children depend on it.
请离开那里
Please.
狱长要我们马上撤离
Warden says we got to evacuate.
帮忙把这些运走
Help me get these out of here.
- 那些犯人呢?  - 让他们自生自灭
- What about the inmates?  - Leave 'em.
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 潇妹纸 时间轴:潇妹纸
翻译:水果哥 伊娃 初见 落寞卷菜
校对: 潇妹纸
喂?
Huh?
不错
Hmm.
啊哈
Ahh.
- 这边 放我出去  - 不
- Over here, let me out.  - No.
- 把钥匙给我!  - 不 不行 你太暴力
- Give me the keys!  - No, no, too violent.
- 放了我!  - 你太懒 你太笨
- Take me!  - Sloppy, too stupid.
你呢... 太狂
Too... ambitious.
至于你
You.
我很喜欢你的"职业"
I love your work.
前途无量
Big future.
嘿 出去后要小心
Hey, be careful.
余震会不断来袭的
There's liable to be aftershocks.
哦 我还挺期待的呢
Oh, I'm counting on it.
绿箭侠 第二季 第七集
Queen先生 你母亲的案子怎么样了?
Mr. Queen, what are your mother's chances?
她是在接受防自杀观察吗?
Is she on suicide watch?
Queen先生 有什么想说的吗?
Mr. Queen, can you give us any comment?
这不公平 他们又不是要受审的人
It's not fair. They're not the ones on trial.
Jean Loring会一直用他们来博取大众同情的
That won't stop Jean Loring from using them as props to drum up sympathy.
你似乎对此不太关心
You don't seem overly concerned.
她在电视直播中承认自己是共犯
She confessed to being an accomplice on live television.
她还说是Malcolm Merlyn强迫她的
She also sad that Malcolm Merlyn coerced her.
你掌握了什么?
You have something, don't you?
Adam 我认为作为合伙律师
I thought I was your co-counsel, Adam.
如果你掌握了本案的关键证据 难道不应该告诉我吗?
If you're holding a trump card, don't you think maybe you should share it with me?
这将是一场别开生面的审判
It's going to be a good trial.
进去吧
Come on, let's get inside.
你们没必要赶尽杀绝
You don't have to do this.
Ivo给我们下的命令
Ivo says we do.
你的朋友对他们是个威胁
Your friends are a danger to his men.
闭嘴 快点走
Go. Quick and quiet.
Slade! Shado! 快跑!
Slade! Shado! Run!
里面没人
There's no one here.
他们一定逃跑了
They must have moved on from their position.
炸弹已安好 这是引爆器
Chargers are set. Here's the detonator.
让他们在这里无处藏身
Make sure they have no place to return to.
去吧
Go.
至于你
And you.
给我们带路去墓地
Now you're going to take us to the graves.
走吧 把他弄起来
Let's go. Get him up.
注意四周
Let's get clear.
找到引爆装置了吗?
Did you find the detonator?
找到了
Yes.
我们很幸运
We were lucky.
我很幸运 你是幸运女神
I was lucky. You were good.
随便怎么说吧...
Either way...
他们抓住了Oliver
They have Oliver.
我要去救他
I'm going after him.
我跟你一起
Not alone.
你走路都费劲
You can barely walk.
这里不能久留
All the more reason not to stay here.
不能让他们再来把我炸飞
Give them another chance at blowing me up.
你们还好吧?
Are you two ok?
这个问题应该我来问你
I should be asking you that question.
我没事
I'll be fine.
你好像得了流感
You look like you have the flu.
要是得了流感 那当初的疫苗就白接种了
If that's true, I shouldn't have wasted my time getting vaccinated.
Diggle 不管怎样 你还是回去休息一下吧
Diggle, whatever it is, just go home.
Oliver 我没事
Oliver, listen, I can take care of things.
我们不会有事的
No, we'll be fine, all right?
回去休息吧 别逼我叫警察把你拖回去
Go rest. And don't make me call a cop.
有几个警察在附近哟
There are a few of them around here.
我被迫参与
I have been complicit in an undertaking
一项恐怖的阴谋...
with one horrible purpose...
摧毁贫民区的一切
to destroy the Glades and everyone in it.
阴谋得逞了 贫民区被摧毁了
And it worked. The Glades were destroyed.
人们流离失所
Homes and lives were lost.
全都归罪于她
All because of her actions.
虽然她悔过了
True, she had second thoughts, remorse which
因自责而发表了以上声明
compelled her to deliver this statement.
但作为那天
But on behalf of the 503 lives
丧生的503人的代表
that were extinguished that day,
我觉得Moira Queen的自责声明来的太迟了
I say, Moira Queen, your remorse comes too late.
在过去的五年里
For the last five years,
他以我和我家人的生命
under the threat for my life
来威胁我...
and the lives of my family...
为什么这些威胁会让她妥协?
Why wouldn't those threats silence her?
为什么Moira Queen非常害怕?
Why wouldn't Moira Queen be terrified?
因为Malcolm Merlyn谋杀了她的第一任丈夫
Malcolm Merlyn killed her first husband,
然后绑架了她的第二人丈夫 她怎么能不担忧自己的生命呢?
abducted her second. Why wouldn't she be in fear for her life?
怎么能不担心她孩子的安危呢?
For the lives of her children?
你碰到这种情况会怎么做?
What would you do?
要是你孩子的生命
If it were your children in the crosshairs
被一个疯子威胁 你会怎么做?
of a mad man's rage?
他们说S.T.A.R.实验室的粒子加速器
They say S.T.A.R. Lab's particle accelerator
将会按计划开启
will be turned on right on schedule.
来自其他方面的报道
In other news, we have just received word
有消息称控辩双方就Moira Queen的案子
that both sides have now completed their opening statements
都做了陈述
in the Moira Queen trial.
别误会 我觉得你看起来很不好
Don't take this the wrong way, but you look disgusting.
没错 Felicity 我是不太舒服
Yeah, well, I don't feel great, Felicity.
要怎么才能好点呢?
Is there a right way to take that?
你应该回去休息
You should go home.
就要回去了
I am going.
我要安排一个替班保镖
I just need to make arrangements for a replacement bodyguard.
你接种过防流感疫苗吗? 我是没有
Did you get the flu shot? Personally, I never do.
虽然知道有必要接种 但是我晕针
I know that I should. I just, I have this thing about needles.
所有尖的东西 我都害怕
All pointy things, really.
讽刺的是 我们还得跟用弓箭的人搭伙工作
Which is ironic, considering who we work with.
这不是流感 Felicity 感觉更像是...
Yeah, it's not the flu, Felicity, it's more like...
Dig! 你怎么了?
Dig!
有人吗?
Hello?
你在吗?
Are you here?
在这里... 在那里...
Here... there...
无处不在
Everywhere.
那么
So.
我们的科研进展如何?
How goes our little science project?
跟你预期的一样
Working like you said it would.
真不错
How wonderful.
听我说
Ah, so listen.
研究的薪酬是五万块
Doing the thing was 50,000.
要想让我封口的话
Keeping quiet about it,
就得给我二十五万
I'm thinking it should be 50 more.
是吗
Hmm.
我不需要封口
Oh, I want word to spread.
实际上 这是我计划的一部分
It's kind of the whole objective, actually.
懂我的意思吗?
You see my point?
你应该知道 事后谈判...
You should know, I find post hoc negotiation...
收场不会愉快的
Distasteful.
啊
Ahh.
真遗憾 医生
Such a shame you won't get to see
你看不到自己的杰作了
what your works have wrought, doctor.
但是过不了多久 大家都会感受到的
But soon, everyone else will.
而他们会求我结束痛苦
And they'll beg for me to end.
你怎么会在这里?
What the hell are you doing here?
我听说你晕倒了?
I heard you passed out.
我告诉Felicity不要给你打电话
I told Felicity not to call you.
没错 在此之前 你还说了"水沟" 和"子弹"
Yeah, but before that, you said "gaw" and "thud,"
不过我没太在意
So I didn't take it very seriously.
他给我电话是明智之举 Diggle 你需要去医院
She was right to call me. Diggle, you need medical attention.
他需要的不止是去医院 Dig昏厥的时候
He needs more than that. When Dig passed out,
我采集了他的血液样本 送到一位搞质量检测的化学师那里检测
I sent a sample of his blood to a chemist I know at QC.
那家伙欠我一个人情 一言难尽 我帮他搞定了违章罚单
The guy owes me a favor. Long story, I fixed his parking ticket.
啊哈 也不是一言难尽
Huh. I guess it's not that long.
Felicity 重点是血液样本检测
Felicity. The blood sample.
没错 检测结果显示... 迷魂药检阳性
Yeah. It came back positive... for trace amounts of vertigo.
我从来没服用过迷魂药
I never used vertigo before in my life.
可能是无意间摄入的
You were exposed to it somehow.
迷魂药又出现了?
Vertigo's in play again?
"伯爵"从他的迷魂药恢复过来后
When the count recovered
被送到了铁山监狱
from his od on vertigo, he was sent to Iron Heights.
那里被地震破坏了
That got hit in the quake.
他和那个"洋娃娃制作师"一样越狱了吗?
He got out the same way the doll maker did?
就跟那个案犯一样
And just like with the doll maker,
监狱官方发言一直在掩盖事实
Prison officials worked overtime to keep the lid on the escape.
- 我知道你想做什么  -  不 你不知道
- I know what you're thinking.  - No, you don't.
我曾经放了他一命
I made a choice not to put an arrow in this guy.
当时的决定是对的
And it was the right choice.
我不会再杀戮
There's no more killing.
我要消除迷魂药这个祸患
I worked this up to counteract the effects of vertigo.
给Diggle注射这个 我...
Give it to Diggle. I...
我还要回法庭
I need to get back to court.
这段时间 你尽量查一下
While I'm gone, just work up whatever you can
Diggle是怎么在不知不觉中摄入迷魂药的
and figure out how Diggle got vertigo in his system without his knowledge.
交给我吧
Ok. Go.
你是什么时候知道关于这场阴谋的消息?
When was the first time you heard about this so-called undertaking?
跟大家一样 在我母亲现场发表声明的时候
When everyone else did, when my mother gave the press conference.
看起来你有点接受不了?
Doesn't seem like you took it too well.
我很震惊
I was surprised.
大家都很震惊
Who wouldn't be?
你母亲在那之后很快被拘捕
Uh, your mother was, um, immediately take into custody,
我可以假设你去监管区探望过她?
but I assume you went down to the precinct to see her?
事实上 我在她被转移之后才去看过她
Um, actually I didn't see her until she was moved.
去监狱看望
To the prison.
你记得是什么时候去见她的吗?
Do you remember when you visited her?
呃 记不起确切的日期了
Uh, not the exact date.
没关系 我这有拜访者记录
It's ok. I have the visitor log here.
10月9日
October ninth.
五个月之后
Five months later.
为什么这么久?
Why so long?
呃 我... 我...
Um, I... I...
你没事吧?
Are you ok?
请回答
An answer, please.
为什么要等五个月之后才去看你妈妈?
Why did it take you five months to visit your mother?
- 法官大人 如果我...  - 不
- Your honor, if I...  - No.
我也想听下
I want to hear this.
我需要时间
I needed time.
我当时...
I was...
愤怒 也许是很愤怒
Angry. So angry, perhaps,
以致于你要5个月后才原谅她?
that it took you five months to forgive her?
是百感交集
It was complicated.
不 其实很简单
No. It's very simple.
你责怪你母亲的所作所为
You blamed your mother for what she had done.
那陪审团为什么不可以责怪?
So why shouldn't the jury?
法官大人 我们对... 证人
Your honor, we have no further questions
没有其他问题了
for the... witness.
噢 Adam!
Adam!
在哪里?
Where is it?
说啊 到底在哪里?!
Come on, where is it?!
回转石在哪里?
The hosen, where is it?
什么?
What?
箭头
The arrowhead.
报道都说和这些尸体一起的
Every report said it was with these bodies.
你说你和你朋友来过这
You said you and your friends were here.
快说在哪?
Now, where is it?
带他出去
Take him outside.
让他指出他朋友的藏身之处
Make him show you where his friends are hiding.
带我们去找他们
Take us to them.
我不知道他们在哪!
I don't know where they are!
噢!
Oww!
告诉我 否则你的手就废了
Tell me, or you lose your hand.
我们选另外一条路
Let us suggest another option.
把他交过来 就留你们几条生命
You hand the kid over to us, and we don't kill you all.
喂 你没事吧?
Hey, are you ok?
别担心 我承受得住
Don't worry about me. I can take it.
是不是真的那么糟糕?
Was that as bad as it seemed?
你说Thea的证词吗? 现在中场休息了
Thea's testimony? It was a set-back.
我们指望她...
We were counting on her to...
让我人性化点
Humanize me.
坦白说 对的
Frankly, yes.
现在我们得用其他方式了
And now we're going to have to go another way.
不 不 我跟你说过 我不要作证
No. No, I told you, I won't testify.
你说过 但是现在必须作证了
I know you did. But now you have to.
她说的没错 妈妈
She's right, mom.
Jean 可以让我们私谈一下吗?
Jean, can you give us a minute?
好的
Yeah.
我知道你要说什么
I know what you're going to say.
但如果我作证的话 就会毁掉我们的家
But if I testify, it will destroy our family.
如果你的律师没错的话 你没有其他选择
And if your lawyer's right, you don't have a choice.
妈妈 就是因为秘密导致你现在的处境
Mom, secrets are what put you in this situation.
秘密和谎言
Secrets and lies.
现在是时候
And now it is time
说真话了
to give the truth its day.
现在 我不想大家忽略
Now, I don't want us to lose sight
今天法庭发生的另外一个重大事件
of the other major event in court today.
有征兆显示Adam Donner病了吗?
Was there any indication of Adam Donner being ill?
没有 在Donner先生晕倒之前没有任何预兆
No, there was very little warning before Mr. Donner collapsed to the ground.
我问过出席法庭的几个人...
I've spoken to several people that were in the courtroom with me...
你感觉怎样?
How are you feeling?
还好
Fine.
你面无表情 Diggle
You have a lousy poker face, Diggle.
他吃解药了吗?
Did he take the antidote?
没用 "伯爵"肯定在他的处方做了手脚
Didn't work. The Count must have futzed with his recipe.
听说Donner的事了
Heard what happened with Donner
在法庭上和Thea的事
at the court, and with Thea.
她怎么样?
How is she?
会没事的
Going to be fine.
你也面无表情 和我差不多 Oliver
Your poker face isn't much better than mine, Oliver.
- 你好 Starling市  - Felicity!
- Hello, Starling City.  - Felicity!
想我吗?
Miss me?
你们多数人应该感觉到身体不适吧...
Many of you have noticed that you're not feeling quite like yourselves...
他占领了当地所有的食物站
He's taken over all the local station feeds.
追踪信号发射地
Track his signal.
和我们能干的助理检察官一样
Like our good assistant district attorney here.
你们大概已经从在审的
You might recognize him from his work
Moira Queen案上认识了他
in the ongoing Moira Queen trial.
- 喂 Adam  - 你想怎样
- Hi, Adam.  - What do you want?
我想如你所愿
I want what you want.
让你感觉好点
For you to feel better.
见鬼去吧!
Go to hell!
我觉得你也想结束痛苦了
I do think you want the pain to end,
我可以...
and I can do that...
用迷魂药帮你
with vertigo.
这就是你身体渴望的
It's what all of your bodies crave.
幸运的是 解药就在这
Fortunately, the power of relief is right here.
你只需去找你家附近
And all you have to do is go to your friendly
友善的迷魂药经销商寻求解药
neighborhood vertigo dealer and request the cure.
只是简单供求关系
Simply supply and demand at work.
只要说你想要
Now, tell me you want this
它就是你的了
And it's yours.
所有痛苦就会... 消失
All the pain will just... disappear.
说吧
Say it.
说...
Say...
你想要
You want it.
我... 我... 想... 我想要
I... I... want... I want it.
你看... 多简单的解决办法
You see... a simple solution.
我是迷魂药伯爵
I'm Count Vertigo,
批准你如此销魂
And I approve this high.
现在怎么办?
What do we do now?
去找他...
We find him...
然后干掉他
and shut him down
他是在哪拍的?
Where did he broadcast from?
他弹回了S.T.A.R.实验室卫星的信号
He bounced the signal off of S.T.A.R. Lab's satellite.
有可能是从Markovia发来的
He could have sent that transmission from Markovia.
他肯定会以当地会据点
He would want to stay local.
分解画面 若有必要 就一帧一帧来
Scrub the footage, frame by frame if you have to.
这上面有线索 我们可以找到
There's something on here that gives us a clue
- 他的位置  - 如果他给整座城市下药了
- to where he is.  - If he dosed the whole city,
为什么只有部分人有症状?
why are only some people showing symptoms?
可能是有选择的
Maybe exposure was selective.
"伯爵"在一些只有部分人群
Count contaminated something that only certain people,
像你和Donner使用的东西中下药了
like you and Donner, consumed.
最戏剧性的改变
A most dramatic turn.
城市高官都在维稳
City officials are urging calm,
希望不会引起大规模恐慌
hoping to avoid widespread panic.
Levitz副市长有...
Deputy Mayor Levitz has...
"伯爵"把Starling市变成了吸毒城
The Count has turned Starling into a city of junkies.
追踪到他藏Adam Donner的地点了吗?
Any leads on where he's holding Adam Donner?
不 心寒的是 我有其他担忧了
Hmm, no. As cold as it sounds, I've got other concerns.
Laurel啊?
Laurel?
Adam的审讯笔记很详细
Adam's trial notes are very thorough.
最好是这样 你现在首席律师了
They better be. You're lead counsel now.
Spencer女士 你可是地方检察官啊
Ms. Spencer, you're the district attorney.
对 但陪审团只认识你
Yes, but you're the one that the jury knows.
你可以做好的 Laurel
You'll do fine, Laurel.
我知道
I know.
我刚发现Adam的杀手锏了
I just found Adam's trump card.
我想自己清静下
I just want to be left alone.
可惜你做不了主
Well, too bad that's not an option for you.
但我知道这样有用
But maybe I know something that is.
打我
Hit me.
什么?
What?
你知道为什么我以前总是晚上出去
You wonder why I used to go out at night
和坏家伙们打架吗?
looking to throw down with bad guys?
一方面是为了帮助这个城市
Part of it was to help the city.
另一方面是
And the other part
帮助自己
was to help me.
揍街头小混混对你有帮助?
Getting tuned up by street thugs helped you?
对 我有付出也有收获
Yeah, well, I gave as good as I got.
我们试试
There we go.
我想出拳打架时 感觉很愤怒
When I would throw a punch, I'd be so angry.
有一团火在我内心燃起
I'd feel this heat rising inside of me,
在下巴 在心中
in my jaw. In my chest.
和拳头上
And my fists.
但我得暂时躲一躲
But I needed somewhere to go.
来
Come on.
Thea 你很不爽
Thea, you're angry.
因为你妈妈 因为律师事务所 还有你自己
At your mother, the D.A., yourself, maybe.
如果你不发泄出来
But that anger is going to chew up your insides
愤怒就会吞噬你
if you don't let it out.
我不想揍你 Roy
I'm not going to hit you, Roy.
试一下
Try.
试一下!
Try!
我说的是揍我 对吧? 你这样...
I said hit me, right? 'Cause that felt like...
根本不算
that didn't really feel like anything.
好一点 握紧你的拳头
Better. But keep your wrists straight.
不要只是摆摆胳膊
Don't just use your arm.
要用尽全力
Put your entire body into it.
再来一次
Come on, again.
至少让我给Lyla打个电话吧
At least let me call Lyla.
那样只会让她担心我
All she could do is worry about me.
我有新发现
I found something.
我没看明白
I don't see anything.
因为你还没看到Donner看到的
Because you have to see what Donner does.
他眼睛有反射的图像
His eye caught a reflection.
能放大点吗?
Can you enhance?
这都问 真让我伤心
It hurts me that you feel a need to ask.
那是什么 翅膀吗?
What are those, wings?
是一个徽标
It's the city seal.
Starling市政档案部
Starling Municipal Records Department.
自从实行了数字化办公
That building's been abandoned
那栋楼就被弃用了
since the city went to digital. Dollars to donuts,
那里肯定就是伯爵的老巢
that's where the Count is operating out of.
不再是了
Not for long.
你不应该来
You shouldn't be here.
- 我的律师要...  - Moira
- My attorney needs...  - Moira.
我知道跟你谈话可能会让我吊销执照
I know I could be disbarred for speaking with you,
但我不是以律师身份来的
but this isn't something for lawyers.
我想和你谈谈你的家庭
This is a family matter.
Jean告诉我 明天她会提问你
Jean told me she's calling you to the stand tomorrow.
是的
Yes.
但你不能作证
You can't testify.
哦
Well.
Laurel 你不想让我作证
The fact that you don't want me to, Laurel,
更说明我应该作证
is a good indication that I should.
如果你作证 我就必须盘问你
If you take the stand, I’ll have to cross examine you,
那样我就必须竭尽全力
and I’ll have to do it to the best of my ability.
- 我明白  - 不 你不明白
- Yes, I understand.  - No, I don't think you do.
先不说这会给Oliver和Thea带来什么影响
Forget about what this will do to Oliver and Thea.
这些会彻底摧毁你的案子
It also could undermine your entire case.
Moira 求你了
So, Moira, please.
求你了
Please.
别逼我用上这些
Don't make me use this.
现在你在危险关头
Everything is at stake for you.
我不希望是我让你万劫不复
And I don't want to be the one to take it all away.
快一点
Faster, please.
快点! 全城的人都想买
Faster! We have a city full of customers.
千真万确
And I mean this literally.
需求量不断加大 我觉得设备有点不够用
I'm afraid my production apparatus is a little over-taxed
虽然我倒不介意
with the increased demand. I can live with it, though.
但是买家们可不能忍啊
I can't say the city can.
快走
Go.
别动
Be still, my heart.
放开他们
Step away from them.
听说你已经厌倦杀人了
Yes, I’ve heard you've developed an allergy to killing.
- 快点离开!  - 要不然呢?
- Do it!  - Or what?
把我杀了?
You'll kill me?
你真的不再杀人了?
You're really on the no killing wagon?
真是悲哀
Shame.
你错过了人生的一大乐事
Really letting one of life's true pleasures pass you by.
你说过你不想出庭作证了
But you said you didn't want to testify.
但又不得不去
But you have to.
- 为了我  - 不
- Because of me.  - No.
你必须保护好自己
You have to do damage control.
因为你是无辜的
None of this is your fault.
都是受了我的牵连
We're here because of what I did.
你们已经知道了真相
Now, you both know the truth,
但那些不是全部真相
but you don't know all of it.
Laurel知道全部
Laurel does.
她知道什么了?
What does she have?
这些事你们不能从法庭上获知
You shouldn't have to find this out in court.
什么事?
Find out what?
很多年前...
Years ago... it was many yes ago...
你爸爸有很多次...
your father was engaging in his...
很多次外遇
his extramarital activities.
我一时失足
And I had a moment of weakness.
也出轨了
I cheated on him.
和Malcolm Merlyn
With Malcolm Merlyn.
不
No.
不 我...
No, I...
我问过你的
I asked you about this.
去年
Last year.
你说你们俩是清白的!
You said that there was nothing between you two!
宝贝 那都算不上是外遇
There wasn't. Sweetheart, it wasn't an affair.
就是一时冲动 而且过去了很久
It was very brief, and a long time ago.
尽管如此 你还继续和Merlyn先生做朋友
And despite it, you remained friends with Mr. Merlyn.
事实上 他是你们家派对上的常客
In fact, he frequently attended parties at your home.
在我丈夫被杀之前 Malcolm是他的挚友
He was my husband's best friend until Malcolm killed him.
这就是你为什么说
And this is why you claimed to feel
你担心你自己
as though you were in fear for your life
和孩子们的生命安全?
and the lives of your children?
我觉得我完全有理由这么想
Well, I think it's a fairly compelling reason.
去年
Last year,
你的第二任丈夫 Walter Steel
Your second husband, Walter Steel,
被Merlyn先生绑架了 对吧?
was abducted by Mr. Merlyn, is that correct?
是 如你所言
Yes. So you say.
为什么Merlyn没杀Walter 却杀了你的第一任丈夫?
Why didn't Merlyn kill Walter, the same as your first husband?
我说服了Malcolm 没让他那么干
I convinced Malcolm not to.
Malcolm听了你的话
And Malcolm listened to you.
你的朋友饶了Walter一命
Your friend spared Walter's life,
但是你现在却要让陪审团相信
And yet, you'd have this jury believing
你和你的孩子身处危险之中?
That you and your children were in danger?
之前确实是这样的 当时我非常害怕...
We were. I was afraid...
害怕被绳之以法
Afraid of getting caught.
先不说我可能犯了多少幼稚的错误
Despite whatever youthful mistakes I might have made,
Malcolm Merlyn都是一个危险人物
Malcolm Merlyn was a dangerous man.
那是对别人来说
To other people.
但真正对Moira Queen和她的家人
But the only person who truly posed a danger
造成威胁的人
to Moira Queen and her family
是Moira Queen
was Moira Queen.
- 嘿  - 如果你想打我 就动手吧
- Hey.  - Ok, if you want to attack me, go right ahead.
但你该知道 我还没对自己说的话
But you should know that you're not going to say anything
你不能对我说
that I haven't already said to myself.
哇哦 我知道那对你来说很困难
Whoa. I know that that was difficult for you,
我只是想确定你没事
And I just want to make sure that you're ok.
别 别碰我
No, no.
我不理解 在我刚刚那么做之后
I don't understand how you can forgive me
你还能原谅我
After what I just did in there.
我不理解谁会这么心胸宽广
I don't understand how anyone could.
所以 很明显
So, obviously you three
你们三个把回转石从洞里拿了出来
took the hosen out of this cave.
把他抬走
Lift him up.
我知道他没拿
Now I know he doesn't have it,
也就是说你们俩有一个人拿着
which means one of you two does.
交出来 再说交换的事
Give it to me, and we'll discuss an exchange.
我们不知道你在说什么
We don't know what you're talking about.
把Oliver放了
Give us Oliver,
随你们去找
and we'll leave you alone to look for it.
啊!
Aah!
谁还想做蠢事?
Anybody else want to be stupid?
嘿 嘿!
Hey. Hey!
好吧 把他们带走把
Fine. Take 'em.
给他松绑
Cut him loose.
你在干什么?!
What are you doing?!
不能停 他们就在身后!
We have to keep moving, they're following us!
很明显我们会继续跟进
Obviously we're continuing to monitor
今天这两件
both of these major stories
Starling市的重大新闻
in what has become a significant news day here in Starling.
你能告诉我们关于...
What can you tell us about...
Oliver正为他母亲的事烦心
Oliver's going to be pretty wrapped up with his mother.
对于"伯爵"迷魂药如何进入人体
You making any process on how the Count's
你有什么进展吗?
getting vertigo into people's systems?
不多
Not much.
每个点代表一个脱瘾症状者的家
Each dot is the home of somebody with withdrawal symptoms.
看起来没什么规律啊
That seems pretty random.
确实是很随意的分布
That's because it's very random.
好吧
Ok.
如果人们不是在家里接触迷魂药
What if people weren't exposed at home;
而是在工作时候被下药的呢?
what if they got dosed at work?
你能通过工作地点来绘图吗?
Can you do this by their employment addresses?
我真的很好奇
I'm really starting to wonder
那有什么好关注的
What it would take to impress you guys.
看起来像一条线路 一条通往城市的道路
It's a trail. A path through the city.
哪个地方你去过吗?
Any place you've been?
59街和戴尔街 我就是在那儿打的流感疫苗
59th and Dell, that's where I got my flu shot.
你从这些小摊接种疫苗 对吧?
You got your vaccination from one of those trucks, right?
那些只有流动卡车中的一个?
One of those roving flu trucks?
路线
The Route.
这是巡回接种疫苗 Starling市移动医疗站派出的一辆卡车
It's a flu vaccination tour. A truck sent out by Starling City mobile care.
一针之后就能让我上瘾? 这也行?
I got addicted after one injection? That can happen?
当然 有空的话可以试试海洛因
Sure. Try heroin some time.
不能试... 试吧
Not try... try.
好吧 现在卡车在哪儿?
All right, where's the truck now?
市中心 你想怎么做?
Downtown. What do you think?
打给Oliver?
Call Oliver?
不 不 他忙着家里的事呢 我去吧
No, no, he's busy with his family. I'll go.
嘿 不 不能让你去
Yeah, no. That's not happening.
我去吧
I'll go.
Felicity太危险了
Felicity, it's too dangerous.
没事 如果有事 我会给你打电话
It could turn out to be nothing. If it's not, I'll call.
法庭里上演的闹剧你不是刚看见了吗?
Courtroom drama you've just witnessed?
Bethany 没人想到法庭上的形势会急转直下
Bethany, no one expected the turn that testimony took.
Moira Queen和Malcolm Merlyn之间的私情
A revelation that Moira Queen once had an affair with Malcolm Merlyn
成了大家关注的重点
became the sole focus of the prosecution's cross.
有人吗?
Hello?
有人在吗?
Anybody home?
迷魂药 可找到了
Vertigo. Got ya.
有趣吧 嗯?
Funny, eh?
你把我想说的话都说了
You took the word right out of my mouth
Thea啊?
Thea?
今天的审讯结束算是结束了吧?
Can we call it a night?
陪审团刚刚说他们可能要做出裁决
Jury just signaled that they could have a verdict.
法官不会让他们走的 他想今天结束
Judge will not send them home. He wants to get this over with.
糟透了
Line forms behind me.
这么快就裁决 不是好事吧?
A verdict that quickly is bad, isn't it?
你俩应该做最坏的打算
I think the two of you should prepare for the worst.
抱歉
Excuse me.
Felicity啊...
Felicity...
Oliver啊
Oliver.
这么叫没关系吧?
Is it ok if I call you Oliver?
听到我的声音很吃惊 对吧?
Surprised to hear from me, right?
不过你应该没有我吃惊
Not as surprised as I was.
听着 我发现一个
You see, I find this
不怎么漂亮的金发在扰乱我的生意
not unattractive blonde getting all up in my business.
她戴着什么呢?
And what does she have on her?
Queen氏实业的工作证
A Queen Consolidated I.D. Badge.
这个名字怎么这么熟悉呢?
Now, I think to myself, why does that name ring a bell?
原来是Oliver Queen
Oliver Queen.
去年兜帽男把我投进监狱之前
He tried to buy off me last year,
他想收买我
just before the hood put me in a padded cell.
也就是你 绿箭侠
Ipso facto, Arrow.
你去哪儿?!
Where are you going?!
哦...
Oh...
办公室有点事情
Something's come up at the office.
Ollie 陪审团怎么办!
Ollie, the Jury!
我一定要去
I have to go.
奢侈豪华的办公楼
Pretty swanky offices.
从这儿就可以看到
You can see all the destruction that your mom caused
你妈妈搞的破坏
from up here.
你想怎样?
What do you want?
世界和平 自我实现
World peace and personal satisfaction.
也不一定要按这个顺序走
Though not necessarily in that order.
你给我下毒 把我扔进洞里
You poisoned me and put me in a hole.
你无法想象 我有多恨你
You have no idea how much I hated you for that.
不过 有人跟我一样对你恨之入骨
Turns out, someone else hates you, too.
- 谁?  - 谁?
- Who?  - Who?
哦 等你知道了 一定会大吃一惊
Oh, you're going to be surprised when you find out.
他是个吝啬鬼
He's a man of means.
给我重新安排了手术 让我引蛇出洞
Set me up with my new operation so I could draw you out.
- 做什么?  - 杀了你
- To do what?  - This.
你要再用点功夫了
You're going to have to try harder.
没问题!
Done!
- 站起来!  - 啊!
- Come on!  - Ahh!
现在让我们执行计划B
So now we move on to plan B.
Oliver 别! 别为了我破戒!
Oliver, don't! Not for me!
安静 谢谢 我在威胁他
Quiet, please. I'm threatening.
放下你的箭
Lower your bow.
你和我之间的恩怨
Your problem is with me.
别牵扯到她
It's not with her.
把这当作是你逼我执行计划B
Well, then, consider this your penalty
所付出的代价吧
for making me go to plan B in the first place.
嘿 嘿
Hey. Hey.
嘿 嘘 嘘
Hey, shh, shh.
没事了
It's all right.
你安全了
You're safe.
哦 你中枪了
Oh, you were shot.
嘿
Hey.
没事的
It's nothing.
有什么进展么?
Any news?
你去哪儿了?
Where have you been?
有些事情...
Something...
刚在Queen氏实业发生了
happened at Queen Consolidated.
一会你在新闻上就会看见
You will see it on the news later.
别担心
Just don't worry about it.
要是陪审团宣判了怎么办?
What would you have done if there'd been a verdict?
Thea啊...
Thea...
我也不知道该怎么办
I don't know.
你还好吧?
Are you ok?
嘿
Hey.
陪审团回来了
Jury's back.
走吧
Come on.
我收到了陪审团的审判裁决书
I have received a note that the jury has arrived at a verdict.
请公布审判结果
Please publish the verdict.
Star城高级法院
In the superior court of Star County
宣布对Moira Queen的裁决...
State versus Moira Queen verdict...
就一级阴谋的指控
On one count of conspiracy in the first degree,
被告人被判定无罪
the defendant is found not guilty.
就谋杀503人案的指控
On the 503 counts of murder in the first degree,
被告人被判定...
The defendant is found...
无罪
not guilty.
妈妈
Mom.
我爱你们
I love you both so much.
判决结果令人震惊 就所有指控 Moira Queen被判无罪
A stunning result, as Moira Queen is acquitted of all charges.
今天的判决是本周最让人震惊的事件 也是法律的扭曲
In a day that's provided a week's worth of shocks and legal twists,
很多人认为该案已成定局
many had pronounced this case a done deal.
祝贺
Congratulations.
- 该祝贺吗?  - 她应该败诉
- Is that appropriate?  - She should have lost.
应该被判有罪
She should have been convicted.
你希望她被判有罪吗?
Did you want her to be?
我希望
I expected her to be.
陪审团的裁决没什么意义
Verdict doesn't make sense.
不过 你妈妈一定很兴奋
Still, your mom must be thrilled. Beyond.
我觉得 更多的是震惊
It's more like shock, I think.
她正在办理手续 我来看看你的情况
They're processing her now. I just wanted to check in on you.
还有你的
And you.
感觉好多了
I'm feeling better.
有了迷魂药被污染的疫苗
And, with the vertigo tainted vaccine,
Queen实业应用科学部门
Queen Consolidated's applied sciences division
应该能研究出防上瘾治疗方案
was able to formulate a non-addictive treatment.
很好
Good.
我要回去和家人聚一聚
I need to meet my family at home.
你们也回家休息吧
So you guys go home, get rest.
晚安
Good night.
Oliver 我 呃...
Oliver. I, uh...
- 我想说 谢谢你  - 心领了
- I just wanted to say thank you.  - Yeah.
抱歉
And I'm sorry.
抱歉什么?
For what?
我又一次惹上麻烦
I got myself into trouble again,
迫使你... 杀了他
And you... killed him.
你又杀人了 很抱歉
You killed again, and I am sorry that I was the one
我让你进退两难 不得不做出这种决定
to put you in a position where you had to make that kind of choice.
Felicity啊...
Felicity...
他劫持你 并且想要伤害你
He had you, and he was going to hurt you.
我别无他选
There was no choice to make.
为什么这么做?!
Why did you do that?!
因为你从队长手上救了我的命
Because you stopped the Captain from killing me.
谢谢你来救我
Thank you for coming.
Shado 他看起来状况很糟
Shado, he doesn't look too good.
- 他还好  - 这又是谁?
- He's not.  - Who's this?
一言难尽 他们要找的回转石
It's complicated. That hosen thing
还在飞机残骸上
they're looking for is back on the plane.
不 在我这里
No, I've got it.
它的一面上刻有佛经
It has a Buddhist inscription on one side.
让我想起了我父亲
It reminded me of my father.
我可以肯定 他们感兴趣的不是佛经
I'm pretty sure they aren't interested in Buddhism.
另一面是什么?
What's on the other side?
数字 30-30-175-12
30-30-175-12.
数字 是什么...
Ok, numbers, what...
是坐标
Coordinates.
什么坐标?
To what?
二战时期日本在此搁浅的潜艇的坐标
A Kairyu-class Japanese submarine which ran aground here during world war II.
这些人找一艘七十年前的潜艇干什么?
What do these guys want with a 70 year old sub?
潜艇不是重点 重要的是它运载的东西...
The sub isn't important, but what's on it...
它能够拯救人类
It'll save the human race.
能拯救他吗?
Will it save him?
你竟然没蠢死 祝贺啊
Well, you survived your own stupidity, congratulations.
你知道...
You know...
曾经我需要你
I needed you
帮我摆平岛上的
to deal with any resistance
一切烂摊子 不得不说
that I encountered on the island. I got to say,
你做的很差
You've done a fairly lousy job of that.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
你现在是新任队长
You're the new Captain.
我安排"伯爵"去除掉绿箭侠
I arranged for the count to take out the arrow,
结果呢
And all I accomplish is reigniting
只是燃起了他的杀人欲望
the vigilante's killing spree.
长官 有进展
Sir, there's been a development.
Cyrus兄弟...
Brother Cyrus...
感觉如何?
How do you feel?
更加强壮了
Stronger.
很好
Good.
你可以上场了
Then you're ready.
Queen夫人 摆脱谋杀的指控感觉如何?
Mrs. Queen, how does it feel to get away with murder?
到后边去 会有车接你
Once you go out back, there's a car waiting for you.
是你谋杀了自己的第一任丈夫吗?
Did you kill your first husband?
一直走就行
Just keep going.
显然Queen夫人很高兴陪审团认为
Obviously Mrs. Queen is overjoyed that the jury
她是在生命被威胁的情况下的无奈之举
has ruled that she was acting under terrible duress.
还有别的信息吗?
Can you give us anything else?
这边走 Queen夫人
This way, Mrs. Queen.
走高速公路能更快
The freeway will be quicker.
抱歉 Queen夫人
I'm sorry, Mrs. Queen.
我不是载你回家的
I was instructed not to take you home.
还不能回去
Not yet.
这是什么地方?
Where are we?
我... 我没来过这里
I... I don't know this place.
先生 我把她带来了
I've got her, sir.
你好 Moira
Hello, Moira.
你不是死了吗?!
They said you were dead!
死亡对于世界上的某些人来说只是假象
There are parts of the world where death is an illusion.
我就是其中一员
I've been to one.
我对此确信无疑
I learned to be very convincing.
但是我回来 是因为你需要我的帮助
But I returned because you needed my help.
帮助?
Help?
帮助解决你的案子
With your trial.
你觉得没有外力协助
You didn't think that jury acquitted you
陪审团会判你无罪吗?
without a little persuasion?
上帝啊
Dear god.
你到底想怎样 Malcolm?
What do you want, Malcolm?
我在Starling市还有一些关系
I still have resources in Starling.
同盟
Associates.
其中
Including one
有一位是检察官
in the D.A.'s office.
我带着极大兴趣关注Donner先生对你的调查
I followed Mr. Donner's investigation of you with interest.
这么多年来 你撒谎撒得那么随意
The ease with which you lied about us for years,
让我怀疑你是不是也有事瞒着我
it made me wonder whether you lied to me.
不 没有
No. No.
做个简单的基因测试
It was a matter of a simple surreptitious genetics test
- 就能轻松解决我的困惑  - 不
- to confirm my suspicion.  - Don't.
当知道Thea是我的女儿
Imagine my joy at learning that
你知道我有多兴奋吗?
Thea is my daughter.
-=圣城家园SCG字幕组 http://hd.cnscg.com/=-
仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
协调: 潇妹纸 时间轴:潇妹纸
翻译:水果哥 伊娃 初见 落寞卷菜
校对: 潇妹纸